Guide to the James R. Houck papers.
Houck, James R. papers.
- Series I. General Documents
  - Summary Report, Undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Level 1 Requirements, Undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Performance Requirements, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - SPIE Paper, Undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - The IRS Version 2.0, 1996-06-14 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - View Graphs, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Proposal for SIRTF/IRS Phase B Study, 1996-1998 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Misc. Proposals, 1997-2003 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - C. Guiar Memos, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Rockwell Science Center Proposals: Closed, 1992-1995 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - A Cryogenic Test Chamber for Future Infrared Detector Development, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Screen Detector, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Misc. Reports, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - IRS Contact Report, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - HBO Lightning Damage, 1995-06 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Misc. IRS Files, 1991-1993 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - SIRTF Overview- TN Gavtier, 1990-10-24 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - IRS Optical Design- J. Baer, 1990-10-12 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - SIRTF IRS IRD?, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - IRS Optical Concept- JR Houck, 1990-10-24 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Misc. Progress Reports, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Experiment Implementation Plan for IRS, 1991-02 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - IRS Status, 1991-03-12 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Ball IRS Notes, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Rockwell Progress Reports, 1987-1991 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Hewitt Info, 1995 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - IPAC Notebook, 1987-06 (Box 53)
  - Gemini Review Notebook, 1993 (Box 53)
  - SIRTF Notebook, Undated (Box 53)
  - AMOWG #1 Notebook, 1992 (Box 53)
  - IRAS #1 Notebook, 1976-1977 (Box 53)
  - Techniques Notebook, 1976 (Box 53)
  - JR Houck Notebook #4, 1976/02/25-1976/06/14 (Box 53)
  - JR Houck Notebook #2, 1975/08/26-1976/02/12 (Box 53)
  - IRMOWG #3/SSB/AMOWG Notebook, 1992 (Box 53)
  - BCandIR Panel #2 Notebook\, 1990 (Box 53)
  - IRMOWG Notebook, Undated (Box 53)
  - Notebook I, Undated (Box 54)
  - Notebook II, 1980 (Box 54)
  - Notebook III, 1980 (Box 54)
  - Notebook IV, 1981 (Box 54)
  - Notebook V, 1982 (Box 54)
  - Notebook VI, 1983 (Box 54)
  - Notebook VII, 1985 (Box 54)
  - Notebook I: "Jim Houck 220 Space Sciences Cornell University", 1975 (Box 54)
  - Notebook II: SIRTF, 1986 (Box 54)
  - Notebook III: SIRTF, 1987 (Box 54)
  - Notebook IV: SIRTF, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Notebook V: SIRTF, 1989 (Box 54)
  - Notebook VI: SIRTF, 1990-1992 (Box 54)
  - Notebook VII: JR Houck, 1992-1994 (Box 54)
  - Notebook VIII: JR Houck, 1994-1995 (Box 54)
  - Notebook IX: JR Houck, 1995-03-1996-04 (Box 54)
  - Notebook X: JR Houck, 1996-04-1997-02 (Box 54)
  - Notebook XI: JR Houck, 1997-03-1998-06 (Box 54)
  - Notebook XII: JR Houck, 2001-05-2002-03 (Box 55)
  - Notebook XIII: JR Houck, 1998-10-1999-07 (Box 55)
  - Notebook XIV: JR Houck, 2000-06-2001-05 (Box 55)
  - Notebook XV: JR Houck, 2001-05-2002-03 (Box 55)
  - Notebook XVI: JR Houck, 2002-03-2003-02 (Box 55)
  - Notebook XVII: JR Houck, 2003-02-2003-12 (Box 55)
  - Notebook XVIII: JR Houck, 2003-12-2005-01 (Box 55)
  - Notebook XIX: JR Houck, 2005-2006 (Box 55)
  - Notebook XX: JR Houck, 2006-2008 (Box 55)
  - Notebook: CONST?, Undated (Box 55)
  - Notebook: CCD Class A410, 1989-2000 (Box 55)
  - Notebook: A410 Lab, 1995-09 (Box 55)
  - Notebook: Palomar #2, 1992-1995 (Box 55)
  - Notebook: Palomar #1, 1990-1991 (Box 55)
  - Notebook: References #2, 2004 (Box 55)
  - Notebook, 1990-1991 (Box 55)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at Cornell University, 2000-03-24-2000-03-25 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at NASA AMES, 2001-03-29-2001-03-30 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at Ball Aerospace, 1999-07-19-1999-07-21 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at NASA AMES, 2001-03-29-2001-03-30 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at Ball Aerospace, 1999-02-12-1999-02-14 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at NASA AMES, 2001-03-29-2001-03-30 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at Cornell University, 2000-03-24-2000-03-25 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at Cornell University, 2001-08-19-2001-08-22 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - SIRTF Science Working Group Meeting Documents, 1998-11-11-1998-11-12 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at Cornell University Documents, 2000-03-24-2000-03-25 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at Ball Aerospace Documents, 1999-02-12-1999-02-14 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at Ball Aerospace, 1999-07-19-1999-07-21 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at Ball Aerospace Documents, 1999-07-19-1999-07-21 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - MIPS Critical Design Review, 1998-07-16-1998-07-17 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - MIPS Critical Design Review, 1998-07-16-1998-07-17 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Combined Electronics Critical Design Review, 1998-08-24 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - CTA Overview/System Engineering Documents, 1998-08-26-1998-08-28 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Observatory Description Document SIRTF, 2000-09-29 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - SIRTF Spectrograph Short-Low/Peakup Module CDR Documents, 1998-02-19 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - IRS Critical Design Review, 1998-08-25 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - SIRTF Infrared Spectrograph Long-Low and Short-High Module CDR Documents, 1998-08-05 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - SIRTF Infrared Spectrogrraph Long-High Module CDR Documents, 1998-06-19 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - IRS and MIPS Combined Electronics Peer Review, 1997-09-08-1997-09-08 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - SIRTF Critical Design Review Vol 3, 1998-09-22-1998-09-24 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - SIRTF Critical Design Review Vol 2, 1998-09-22-1998-09-24 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - SIRTF Critical Design Review Vol 1, 1998-09-22-1998-09-24 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Observatory Performance and Interface Control Document SIRTF, 1998-11-24 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Technical Boeing FPMA Design, 1997-05-09 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - The Infrared Spectrograph Documents, 1995-11-01 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - SIRTF/IRS Si:As and Si:Sb Arrays for Astronomy Technology Review, 1995-07-10 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - SIRTF Infrared Spectrograph Cold Instrument Peer Review, 1997-08-20 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - SIRTF Infrared Spectrograph Short-Low/Peakup Module CDR Documents, 1998-02-19 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - SIRTF Infrared Spectrograph Cold Instrument Peer Review, 1997-08-20 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - SIRTF Independent Annual Review, 1998-10-27-1998-10-28 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - IRS Status at Ball Labs, 1998-10-16 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - SIRTF Infrared Spectrograph Flight Systems Requirements Review, 1997-04-16 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - SIRTF Telescope Acceptance Review, 2001-01-18 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Change Proposal for: IRS Replan for SIRTF April 15, 2003 Launch Delay, 2002-12 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - SIRTF Infrared Spectrograph Short-Low/Peakup Module CDR Documents, 1998-02-19 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Post-Launch Assessment Review SIRTF, 2003-10-23 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Proposal for SIRTF/IRS Phase B Study, 1996-10-01-1998-03-31 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Multiband Imaging Photometer for the SIRTF Phase C/D Instrument Implementation, 1997-07 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - U25-8455 (NSG 2412) Molecular Spectroscopy from the Kuiper Airborne Observatory, 1983-11-01-1984-10-31 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Observatinos of Mid-Infrared Fine-Structure Line Emission from Gaseous Nebulae: Determination of Abundances, 1983-11-01-1983-10 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Technical Current Documents, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - SIRTF Talk Materials, 1983-1985 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Misc SIRTF Reports, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - KAO Correspondence, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Journal Communications (includes letters, references, reports, memos on publication formats, etc), 1987 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - KAO Meeting Agenda, 1988-05-23 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - KAO User's Meeting Agenda, 1987-03-20 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - KAO User's Bulletin, 1988-01-20 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - KAO Meeting Documents, 1986-12-18 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - SWG Meeting Minutes, 1984-12-17-1984-12-19 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Memoranda, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - AMOWG Telemail, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Misc PALOMAR Documents, 1992-1995 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Misc PALOMAR Documents, 1993-1994 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - DIT Photos and Documents, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Infrared Spectrometer Slides, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Atomic Viewgraphs, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Infrared General, 1979 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Infrared Spectrometer, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Gemini Review Committee Findings (CAA Gemini), 1993-05-04 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Palomar Proposals, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Series II. Correspondence Regarding SIRTF (Space Infrared Telescope Facility) and IRS (Infrared Spectrograph)
  - Correspondence, 1990-12 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1990-11 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1990-09-1990-10 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1990-08 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1990-07 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1990-06 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1990-04-1990-05 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1990-02-1990-03 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1989-12-1990-01 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1989-10-1989-11 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1989-08-1989-09 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1989-06-1989-07 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1989-03-1989-05 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1988-12-1989-02 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1988-09-1988-11 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1988-02-1988-08 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1987-02-1988-01 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - SIRTF-IRS Email Correspondence, 1998-06-20-1998-08-31 (Box 6)
  - SIRTF-IRS Email Correspondence, 1998-09-01-1998-11-30 (Box 6)
  - SIRTF-IRS Email Correspondence, 1998-12-01-1998-03-14 (Box 6)
  - SIRTF-IRS Email Correspondence, 1999-03-15-1999-06-15 (Box 6)
  - SIRTF-IRS Email Correspondence, 1999-11-16 (Box 7)
  - SIRTF Email Correspondence, 1999-06-16-1999-11-15 (Box 8)
  - SIRTF Correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Ball Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Ball Correspondence, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Ball Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Contact Reports and Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Rockwell Correspondence, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Rockwell Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Series III. Palomar Related Material
  - Palomar Observing Proposals and Emails, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Papers Relating to Norris Foundation, 1996-2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Palomar Observatory Instrumentation, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Palomar Student Travel and Engineering Reports, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Palomar Observatory Use Requests, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports of the Palomar Observatory, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Annual Reports of the Palomar Observatory, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Annual Reports of the Palomar Observatory, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - SpectroCam-10 User's Manual, 1994-11-28 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Information Regarding Double SpectroGraph, 1990-1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Information Regarding Four Shooter Camera, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Information Regarding Infrared Equipment, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Time Allocation Forms, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Time Allocation Forms, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    Note on Folder: mostly light pollution
  - Palomar Observing Schedule, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Palomar Proposal Review, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Palomar Proposal Review, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Agreement with Caltech, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Information Regarding Spectrograph Problem, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - CCJ Meeting Records, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Original folder kept because of equations on inside
  - Palomar Instruments: an informal overview, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Cornell at Palomar Presentation, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Note on Folder: Presentation to Dean Phil Lewis
  - Transparencies, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Palomar Correspondence, 1991-1996 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Palomar Observation Manual, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - CCD Operation Manual, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Palomar View Graphs, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Palomar Project Communication, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Note on Folder: 9:05 AM M or F
  - Early Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Original folder kept because of writing
  - Miscellaneous Information, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Palomar Observation Schedule, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Palomar Proposal Review, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Palomar Proposal Review, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Palomar Proposal Review, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Palomar Observation Schedule, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Palomar Proposal Review, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Palomar Proposal Review, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Palomar Observation Schedule, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Palomar Proposal Review, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Palomar Users' Guide, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Series IV. Shuttle Infrared Telescope Facility (SIRTF)
  - SIRTF Requirements and Approved Parts, 1990-11-20 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Interoffice Memorandum, 1991-01-22 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - SIRTF Multiple Instrument Chamber Reconfiguration Study, 1991-05 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Packet Telemetry, 1987-12-1992-11 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - SIRTF Promotional Materials, 1984-1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ge:Ga and Ge:B BIB Detector Array Workshop, 1993-11-17 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - NASA Project Management Issues Vol I-IV, Undated (Box 8)
  - Rochester Accounts Payable Papers, 1991-01-1997-02 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Subcontract with Penn State, 1996-01-1997-02 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Subcontract with University of Rochester, 1992-01-1997-02 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - SIRTF Progress Reports, 1995-06-01-1996-05-01 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - SIRTF Progress Reports, 1994-07-01-1995-05-31 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Subcontract with Ball Aerospace and Technologies, 1992-01-1997-02 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Appropriation Subcommittee Materials, 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - NSF Academic Infrastructure Program Grant Materials, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - SCIENCE Reprints: Infrared Astronomy after IRAS, 1986-1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Reitsema Subcontract Papers, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Astronomy Proposal Materials to NSF, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous items from OSP, 1993-1997 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - NASA HQ Grant Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Boeing Progress Reports, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Rockwell Commercial Shipping Documents, 1993-1999 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Forms and Correspondence, 1993-1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Wire Definition Phase Report, 1995-05 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - SIRTF Account Shared Money, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Subcontracts, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Support Documentation from Ball Aerospace and Technologies, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Quality Assurance Objectives, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Michael Barry Incorporated Materials, 1996-1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Financial Status Reports, 1997-02-1999-12 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - System Engineering Report (SER) Log, 1997-1999 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Brandl License Application Approval, 1999-09-04 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Expense Vouchers, 1999-08-06 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Computer Literature, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Capital Equipment Acquisitioning, 1987-1998 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - SIRTF Metadata and Archives, 1990-1994 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Subcontract with Rockwell and Boeing, 1992-05-1994-12 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Subcontract with Rockwell and Boeing, 1992-05-1994-12 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Subcontract with Rockwell and Boeing, 1994-09-1997-02 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - SIRTF/IRS Promotional Materials, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - ARC-Roellig All Contract Materials, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Penn State Subcontract, 1986-1991 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Caltech Subcontract and Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Reitsema Subcontract, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Reitsema Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Ball-Reitsema Subcontracts, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Forrest Subcontract Modifications, 1988-1991 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Forrest Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    Diagram on folder
  - University of Rochester-Forrest Subcontract, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Watson Subcontract and Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - University of Rochester-Watson Subcontract, 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Ball Subcontract Modifications, 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Former Ball Contracts, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Ball 533Ms Contract and Questions, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Ball Correspondence, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - RISC 533M Contract and Questions, 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - A Proposal Submitted to NASA In Response to RFP for Changes to Contract NAS2-12524, 1987-09 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - SIRTF Reports, 1989-03-1989-05 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - SIRTF Newsletter, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Phase I SIRTF-IRS Study Plan Pt 1, 1987-09 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Phase I SIRTF-IRS Study Plan Pt 2, 1987-09 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Request for Proposal SIRTF Design Study, 1990-06-11 (Box 10)
  - Statement of Work: Penn State, 1987-11 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Statement of Work: Caltech, 1987-11 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Phase I Cost Plan, 1987-09 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Phase I Cost Plan, 1987-11 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Letter of Agreement Between Cornell University and NASA, 1988-02 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Aperture Stop Presentation, 1990-08-04 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Presentation Packets, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Detectors Status Reports, 1989-1992 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Cryogenics Encoder System Engineering Report, 1988-11-17 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Grating Scan Mechanism Documentation Pt 1, 1987-1992 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Grating Scan Mechanism Documentation Pt 2, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Grating Scan Mechanism Blueprints, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Cryogenics Facility Materials, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Edison Mission Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - SIRTF Facilities Documents, 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - SIRTF Technical Papers, 1991-07 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Fine Guidance Sensor Facility Documents, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Spacecraft Conceptual Design Description, 1991-05 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Alternative Mission Study: Final Report, 1989-04 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Floppy Disc and Documentation, Undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Mission Options Study: Final Report, 1989-02-28 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous IRS Papers, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - IRS Cryogenics Reports, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Infrared Array Camera Documents, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Integration Documents, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - SIRTF Industry Briefing, 1990-03-30 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - ICD Facility Configuration, 1987-04 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - SIRTF Scientific Instrument Performance Report (Pre-launch), 2003-01-21 (Box 11)
  - JPL Phonebook, 2002-03 (Box 11)
  - SIRTF Observatory Delta Pre-Ship Review, 2003-02-19 (Box 11)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at NASA AMES, 2001-03-29-2001-03-30 (Box 11)
  - Science Working Group Meeting Agenda, 1993-12-02-1993-12-03 (Box 11)
  - Mission Study for SIRTF Science Objectives with Reduced Cost and Risk: Final Report, 1993-11 (Box 11)
  - Ge:Ga and Ge:B BIB Detector Array Workshop, 1993-11 (Box 11)
  - SIRTF Observatory Pre-Ship Review, 2003-02-19 (Box 11)
  - Combined Electronics Flight Software Detailed Design Document for the IRS and MIPS (Multiband Imaging Photometer), 1998-10-28 (Box 11)
  - Combined Electronics Flight Software Detailed Design Document for the IRS and MIPS (Multiband Imaging Photometer) Pt 2, 1998-10-27 (Box 11)
  - IRS and MIPS Flight Software Peer Review, 1998-01-23 (Box 11)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at Cornell University, 2001-08-19-2001-08-21 (Box 11)
  - IRS Science Team Meeting at NASA AMES, 2001-03-29-2001-03-30 (Box 11)
  - Independent Annual Review, 1998-10-27-1998-10-28 (Box 12)
  - Independent Annual Review, 1999-10-26-1999-10-27 (Box 12)
  - Pre-1996 JPL Communications, 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Pre-1996 JPL Communications, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Programming Code: Clocks, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Programming Code: A/D, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Ge:BIB Paperwork, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Computer File Extensions, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Computer File Extensions, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - FORTRAN Guide, Undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Rockwell-Boeing Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Science Team Memorandums, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Rockwell Progress Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Rockwell Progress Reports, 1997-1999 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Rockwell Progress Reports, 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Infrared Projects Proposal, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Infrared Projects Proposal, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - IRS Pointing Requirements, 1991-05 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Materials on Cryo Properties of Optical Materials, 1974-1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Ball SER on IRS Control System, 1989-12 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - SIRTF Progress Reports, 1995-02-1996-12 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - IRS CDR Reports, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - SIRTF Advertising Material, Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - System Engineering Report, 1990-01 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - SIRTF Reports, 1990-1995 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - SIRTF Project Reviews, 1991-09-1991-10 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Capital Equipment Records, 1991-1998 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Transparencies, 1998-10 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Transparencies, 1993-1995 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    Note on folder: Seneca, Iriquois [sic], Onondaga, Cayuga, Irondiquois
  - Transparencies, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Original folder kept for notes
  - Presentation Materials, 1995-2000 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Transparencies, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Advocacy Materials, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Quality Assurance/Acceptance Testing, 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Quality Assurance Materials, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - SIRTF Office Correspondence, 1990-1997 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Transparencies, 1996-1998 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Cost Estimates, 1994-2001 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Cost Estimates, 1994-2001 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Papers, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Status of the IRS, 1995-09-12 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Report Drafts, 1990-1995 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Papers from Prof Terry Herter: Wide-Field Infrared Explorer, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Grant and Research Proposals, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Grant and Research Proposals, 1994-1997 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Subcontract to BATC, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Proposal Samples and NSF Guide, 1990-1996 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Material Discrepancy Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - SIRTF Progress Reports, 1999-01-2000-02 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - SIRTF Progress Reports, 1997-01-1998-12 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - SIRTF Progress Reports, 1997-03-1997-12 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - System Engineering Report: MIPS Cryogenic Filter Wheel Assembly Final Report, 1990-03-15 (Box 13)
  - SIRTF Payload Technology Plan: Introduction, 1993-05-02 (Box 13)
  - Advertisement, Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - IRS Work Flow Diagram, 1990-10-18 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Consulting Information, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - IRS and MIC (Multiple Instrument Chamber) Documents, 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)